http://www.cas.ca/privacy-policy

Login
French
About CAS
HistoryGovernanceSectionsCommitteesAffiliatesFoundationsCorporate PartnersNational OfficeAdvocacyVolunteer Opportunities
Education
Defining CPD and Related TerminologyContinuing Professional DevelopmentAccreditationWebinars
Practice Resources
COVID-19Guidelines to AnesthesiaCanadian Journal of AnesthesiaAccreditationCAIRSCareer CentreSurveysThe Healthy AnesthesiologistAnesthesia NewsReports and Position PapersCAS Choosing Wisely CanadaNewsResource LibraryForumsUseful Links
Meetings & Events
Annual MeetingEvent CalendarEvents ArchiveWebinars
Awards & Grants
Research ProgramHonour AwardsMedical Student PrizeBest Paper Winners
Membership
Apply for MembershipRenew Your MembershipResidents & TraineesMember Benefits
Privacy Policy
By using this website and/or CAS services, you acknowledge that you have read and understood this statement and consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as set out below.
For Members:
Members' names and addresses will not be used by CAS for commercial purposes unless related to member benefits or sponsorship programs. If you are a CAS Board, Section or committee member, your name and address may be circulated to the Board and respective committees to facilitate the work of those groups. If you do not wish to supply your personal information, please contact the Executive Director. In addition, Division, Section and Committee Chairs and, in some instances, Committee members will be listed on the CAS website. The same applies to affiliated organizations and foundations including ACUDA, CARF and CASIEF.
For All CAS Website Visitors:
CAS (“we”, “our” or “us”) respects your right to privacy. Personal information is only collected to enable the Society to provide its members, subscribers and meeting registrants with the services to which they are entitled, and to provide general information to the public. It might also be collected to understand your needs and preferences so that we can develop and enhance our services.
When you voluntarily provide us with your personal information, you are consenting to our collection and use of the information for direct CAS use, to provide membership services and benefits. If at any time, you decide you do not wish to receive communications from us, or you no longer wish to receive our services, you may advise us by providing written notice.
All personal information is protected within the CAS office and computer systems. Only staff may access this information, and only on a "need-to-know" basis. Staff must conform to strict procedures for handling and storage. Third party vendors, such as computer support companies, cannot access the CAS network without prior approval and internal assistance for each session.
You have the right to ensure that any information CAS maintains is correct and complete. Upon request, we will supply you with a copy of all personal information we have on record for you. If the information is incorrect, we will change it upon your written request to membership@cas.ca.
Any financial transactions on the CAS website are conducted through a certified secure server and all related transmissions are encrypted. We will retain your personal information only if required to fulfill the purposes we identified to you, unless a longer retention is permitted or required by law.
The privacy rules, security and content of any site you link to from the CAS page are beyond our control and we are not responsible for them.
Questions regarding this policy, or about how your information is collected, used or disclosed, should be directed to CAS Executive Director, who is responsible for our compliance with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act and other applicable privacy legislation.
September 2018
